you
您可以在智能合约中设置
inside the smart contract you can set
state variables to a certain value when
使用特殊合同创建合同时，将状态变量设置为一定值
a contract is created using a special
function called constructor in this
该视频中称为构造函数的函数，我们将介绍基本的
video we're gonna go over the basic
syntax for writing constructors so first
用于编写构造函数的语法，因此首先是构造函数的构造函数是什么
what is a constructor a constructor is
an optional function that is executed
可选功能，仅在创建合同之前执行一次
only once before a contract is created
this function can take in inputs and
该功能可以接受输入，并且可以在功能主体内部设置
inside the function body you can set the
state variables to certain values that
将变量声明为想要的某些值，以便定义构造函数
you want so to define a constructor we
start with the keyword constructor
以关键字构造函数开头，后跟括号，然后在
followed by parentheses and inside the
parentheses be passing some parameters
括号中传递了一些参数，例如，您将传递一些无符号的
for example you'll pass in some unsigned
integers X and Y and we declare the
整数X和Y，我们将构造函数声明为内部的公共函数
constructor as a public function inside
the constructor body we that set some
设置一些变量的构造函数主体
variables
we'll set the unsigned integer X to the
我们将无符号整数X设置为状态变量X，同样将
state variable X and likewise for the
unsigned integer Y finally that's
无符号整数Y最后被声明为状态变量XY
declared a state variable XY
[Music]
[音乐]因此，当我们部署此合同时，
so when we deploy this contract becomes
chapter will be called and it will set
章节将被调用，并将状态变量x和y设置为
the state variables x and y to the
parameters that we passed in let's see
我们传入的参数首先让我们看一个示例并进行编译
an example first go ahead and compile
this contract
这份合同
next we'll deploy the contract but
下一步，我们将部署合同，但是在执行此操作之前，您需要先传递一些
before we do that you'll pass in some
parameters for x and y into the contract
x和y的参数进入合约，您将传递数字1和2并点击
you're passing number 1 and 2 and hit
deploy once the contract is deployed
部署合同后部署，让我们检查一下我们的状态变量x
let's check that our state variables x
and y we're set to the parameters that
和y，我们设置为传递给我们的参数，向下滚动到部署
we passed in scroll down to the deploy
contract and let's check the value for x
收缩，让我们检查x和yx的值等于1且y等于
and y x is equal to 1 and y is equal to
2 that's the exact value that we passed
2这就是我们传递给构造函数的确切值，就像
into our constructor and just like a
regular function a constructor has
构造函数可以访问特殊变量（如消息）的常规函数
access to special variables like message
the sender and block the timestamp let's
发送方并阻止时间戳，让我们将这些特殊变量存储到
store these special variables into a
state variable we will declare two state
状态变量，我们将声明两个状态变量以存储这些变量的值
variables to store the values of these
special variables you'll store message
您将在消息状态中将消息点发件人存储的特殊变量称为状态变量
dot sender in a state variable called
owner and we'll store block that
所有者，我们将把该时间戳记存储在一个状态变量中，该状态变量称为
timestamp in a state variable called
created at once the state variables are
立即定义状态变量创建的代码，让我们将其分配给
defined let's assign them inside the
constructor set the owner to message
构造函数将所有者设置为消息发件人，并创建应用程序以阻止该消息的发送者
sender and created app to block that
timestamp go ahead and recompile this
时间戳记继续，重新编译此合同，然后重新部署和传递
contract and redeploy it and passing
some parameters into the constructor
这次将一些参数传入构造函数中，我将传入3＆4并进行部署
this time I'll pass in 3 & 4 and deploy
it once the new contract is deployed
一旦部署了新合同，让我们检查所有者和
let's check the values of owner and
created at
创建于
for a creative you get the UNIX
对于广告素材，您可以在合同签订时获得UNIX时间戳。
timestamp when this contract was
deployed the owner is set to message the
部署所有者被设置为向发件人发送消息，在这种情况下，发件人是第一个
sender which in this case is a first
account available in remix that covers
可用于混音的帐户，涵盖构造函数的基本语法
the basic syntax for a constructor
in the next video who cover inheritance
在下一个介绍继承的视频中，之后我们将重新审视如何调用
and after that we'll revisit how to call
constructors for parent contracts thanks
父合同的构造函数，感谢您的关注，敬请期待。
for watching and see you in the next
video
视频